https://droghedaunited.ie/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. At Drogheda United FC we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.We don’t share your personal information with anyone.It is Drogheda United FC policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Drogheda United FC collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Drogheda United FC purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Drogheda United FC visitors use its website.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to the Drogheda United FC website choose to interact with Drogheda United FC in ways that require Drogheda United FC to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Drogheda United FC gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, for those who wish to learn more about Drogheda United FC, we collect their name and email address. Drogheda United FC collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Drogheda United FC. Drogheda United FC does not disclose personally-identifying information. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsDrogheda United FC may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. For instance, Drogheda United FC may monitor the most popular pages on the site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Drogheda United FC does not disclose personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Drogheda United FC uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of Drogheda United FC website, and their website access preferences. Drogheda United FC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Drogheda United FC website, with the drawback that certain features of Drogheda United FC website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Drogheda United FC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Drogheda United FC sole discretion. Drogheda United FC encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
+353 (0)41 98 30190
info@droghedaunited.ie
United Park, Windmill Road, Drogheda, A92 F98X
CLUB
Home
News
First Team
Fixtures
Close Menu
We need your consent to use cookies for this website. More information is available in our Privacy policy. You can control your preferences by selecting Cookie Settings. COOKIE SETTINGSACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
×
×Cart
